question_data = [
    {
        "category": "general: Current affairs",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Abuja is the capital of Nigeria.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General: General",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Arctic is the continent in the world.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Science",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Vatican City is with only 0.44 sq.km.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Cinderella was the first Disney princess.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General: General",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": " Football team has 11 players in a team.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: General",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Marrakesh is the capital of Morocco.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General: General",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "M&M stands for Mars and Moordale.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Animal",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The unicorn is the national animal of Scotland.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Animal",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "A lion's roar can be heard up to eight kilometres away.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
